[
  {
    "question": "I spoke to ___.",
    "options": ["she", "her"],
    "correctAnswer": "she",
    "language": "english", 
    "level": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "Where ____ you come from?",
    "options": ["do", "are"],
    "correctAnswer": "do",
    "language": "english", 
    "level": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "What time does she ___ up?",
    "options": ["get", "gets"],
    "correctAnswer": "get",
    "language": "english",
    "level": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "Where ___ he live?",
    "options": ["do", "does"],
    "correctAnswer": "does",
    "language": "english",
    "level": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "'I am not ____ this film.'",
    "options": ["liking", "enjoying"],
    "correctAnswer": "liking",
    "language": "english",
    "level": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "I am seeing her ____ three o'clock.",
    "options": ["in", "at", "on"],
    "correctAnswer": "at",
    "language": "english",
    "level": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "Easter is ___ March this year.",
    "options": ["on", "at", "in"],
    "correctAnswer": "in",
    "language": "english",
    "level": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "She's ____ work all day today.",
    "options": ["at", "on"],
    "correctAnswer": "at",
    "language": "english",
    "level": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "I go ___ home by bus.",
    "options": ["home", "to home"],
    "correctAnswer": "home",
    "language": "english",
    "level": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "'Do you like it?'",
    "options": ["'Yes, I like.'", "'Yes, I do.'"],
    "correctAnswer": "'Yes, I do.'",
    "language": "english",
    "level": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "It's the second road ___ the left.",
    "options": ["in", "at", "on"],
    "correctAnswer": "on",
    "language": "english",
    "level": 1  },
  {
    "question": "He's arriving ___ the station at six.",
    "options": ["at", "on", "to"],
    "correctAnswer": "at",
    "language": "english",
    "level": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "I ___ what she's saying.",
    "options": ["can't understand", "am not understanding"],
    "correctAnswer": "can't understand",
    "language": "english",
    "level": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "She lives ___ London.",
    "options": ["on", "at", "in"],
    "correctAnswer": "in",
    "language": "english",
    "level": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "I'm going ___ the bank to get some cash.",
    "options": ["at", "to"],
    "correctAnswer": "to",
    "language": "english",
    "level": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "I went there ____ foot.",
    "options": ["in", "by", "at", "on", "to"],
    "correctAnswer": "on",
    "language": "english",
    "level": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "____ is a cinema in the shopping centre.",
    "options": ["There", "It"],
    "correctAnswer": "There",
    "language": "english",
    "level": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "____ is it?",
    "options": ["Who's", "Whose"],
    "correctAnswer": "Who's",
    "language": "english",
    "level": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "I went ____ with my sister.",
    "options": ["their", "there"],
    "correctAnswer": "there",
    "language": "english",
    "level": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "She ____ as a doctor.",
    "options": ["is", "works"],
    "correctAnswer": "works",
    "language": "english",
    "level": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "She ___ a doctor.",
    "options": ["is", "works"],
    "correctAnswer": "is",
    "language": "english",
    "level": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "How ___ did your journey take?",
    "options": ["long", "long time"],
    "correctAnswer": "long",
    "language": "english",
    "level": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "He comes ____ the north of the country.",
    "options": ["to", "from"],
    "correctAnswer": "from",
    "language": "english",
    "level": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "She ____ goodbye.",
    "options": ["said", "told", "spoke"],
    "correctAnswer": "said",
    "language": "english",
    "level": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "They are ___ love.",
    "options": ["in", "on", "at", "to", "by"],
    "correctAnswer": "in",
    "language": "english",
    "level": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "You _____ drink and drive.",
    "options": ["may", "must", "may not", "must not"],
    "correctAnswer": "must not",
    "language": "english",
    "level": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "She's studying law ____ university.",
    "options": ["in", "at"],
    "correctAnswer": "at",
    "language": "english",
    "level": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "The bus stopped ___ the traffic lights.",
    "options": ["in", "on", "at"],
    "correctAnswer": "at",
    "language": "english",
    "level": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "She ____ English twice a week.",
    "options": ["study", "studys", "studeis", "studies"],
    "correctAnswer": "studies",
    "language": "english",
    "level": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "____ is it?",
    "options": ["Who's", "Whose"],
    "correctAnswer": "Who's",
    "language": "english",
    "level": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "___ you afford it?",
    "options": ["Do", "Can"],
    "correctAnswer": "Can",
    "language": "english",
    "level": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "They aren't selling ____ tickets.",
    "options": ["much", "many"],
    "correctAnswer": "many",
    "language": "english",
    "level": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "There isn't ______ for all of us to get in.",
    "options": ["room enough", "enough room"],
    "correctAnswer": "room enough",
    "language": "english",
    "level": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "The police ___ called.",
    "options": ["was", "were"],
    "correctAnswer": "were",
    "language": "english",
    "level": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "The police ___ called.",
    "options": ["was", "were"],
    "correctAnswer": "were",
    "language": "english",
    "level": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "In a shop, you are a ____.",
    "options": ["client", "customer"],
    "correctAnswer": "customer",
    "language": "english",
    "level": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "It's bigger ____ the old one.",
    "options": ["as", "than", "then"],
    "correctAnswer": "than",
    "language": "english",
    "level": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "'___ did she do it?' 'Yesterday.'",
    "options": ["Why", "Where", "When", "How"],
    "correctAnswer": "How",
    "language": "english",
    "level": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "How ___ you spell it?",
    "options": ["do", "can"],
    "correctAnswer": "do",
    "language": "english",
    "level": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "How much did you ___ in the shop?",
    "options": ["cost", "spend"],
    "correctAnswer": "spend",
    "language": "english",
    "level": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "'How ___ did you buy?' 'Three kilos.'",
    "options": ["much", "many"],
    "correctAnswer": "much",
    "language": "english",
    "level": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "I don't work ____ the morning.",
    "options": ["on", "in", "at"],
    "correctAnswer": "in",
    "language": "english",
    "level": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "I saw her ___.",
    "options": ["last week", "the last week"],
    "correctAnswer": "last week",
    "language": "english",
    "level": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "It costs ____ dollars.",
    "options": ["forty", "fourty"],
    "correctAnswer": "forty",
    "language": "english",
    "level": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "I heard it ___ the radio.",
    "options": ["in", "at", "on"],
    "correctAnswer": "on",
    "language": "english",
    "level": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "There ____ a lot of complaints.",
    "options": ["was", "were"],
    "correctAnswer": "were",
    "language": "english",
    "level": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "There ____ a lot of sugar in the coffee.",
    "options": ["was", "were"],
    "correctAnswer": "was",
    "language": "english",
    "level": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "He didn't work ____.",
    "options": ["enough hard", "hard enough"],
    "correctAnswer": "hard enough",
    "language": "english",
    "level": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "I ____ her.",
    "options": ["am not knowing", "don't know", "doesn't know"],
    "correctAnswer": "don't know",
    "language": "english",
    "level": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "___ girlfriend left him.",
    "options": ["He", "Him", "His"],
    "correctAnswer": "His",
    "language": "english",
    "level": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "There are too ____ questions in this test.",
    "options": ["much", "many"],
    "correctAnswer": "many",
    "language": "english",
    "level": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "I hope you do ___ in this test.",
    "options": ["good", "well"],
    "correctAnswer": "well",
    "language": "english",
    "level": 0
  },
  {
      "question": "J'ai parlé à ___.",
      "options": ["elle", "la"],
      "correctAnswer": "elle",
      "language": "french",
      "level": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "D'où ____ tu viens ?",
      "options": ["es", "est"],
      "correctAnswer": "es",
      "language": "french",
      "level": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "À quelle heure est-ce qu'elle se ___ ?",
      "options": ["lève", "lèves"],
      "correctAnswer": "lève",
      "language": "french",
      "level": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Où ___-il habite ?",
      "options": ["fait", "est"],
      "correctAnswer": "est",
      "language": "french",
      "level": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "'Je n'aime pas ___ ce film.'",
      "options": ["regarde", "aime"],
      "correctAnswer": "aime",
      "language": "french",
      "level": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Je la vois ____ trois heures.",
      "options": ["à", "de"],
      "correctAnswer": "à",
      "language": "french",
      "level": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Pâques est en ___ mars cette année.",
      "options": ["à", "en"],
      "correctAnswer": "en",
      "language": "french",
      "level": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Elle est ___ travail toute la journée aujourd'hui.",
      "options": ["à", "au"],
      "correctAnswer": "au",
      "language": "french",
      "level": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Je rentre ___ maison en bus.",
      "options": ["à la", "chez"],
      "correctAnswer": "chez",
      "language": "french",
      "level": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "'Tu aimes ça ?'",
      "options": ["'Oui, j'aime.'", "'Oui, j'aime bien.'"],
      "correctAnswer": "'Oui, j'aime bien.'",
      "language": "french",
      "level": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "C'est la deuxième rue ___ gauche.",
      "options": ["sur", "à"],
      "correctAnswer": "à",
      "language": "french",
      "level": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Il arrive ___ gare à six heures.",
      "options": ["à", "de"],
      "correctAnswer": "à",
      "language": "french",
      "level": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Je ___ ce qu'elle dit.",
      "options": ["ne peux pas comprendre", "comprends"],
      "correctAnswer": "ne peux pas comprendre",
      "language": "french",
      "level": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Elle habite ___ Paris.",
      "options": ["sur", "à"],
      "correctAnswer": "à",
      "language": "french",
      "level": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Je vais ___ banque retirer de l'argent.",
      "options": ["à la", "à la"],
      "correctAnswer": "à la",
      "language": "french",
      "level": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "J'y suis allé ___ pied.",
      "options": ["en", "à"],
      "correctAnswer": "à",
      "language": "french",
      "level": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "____ est un cinéma dans le centre commercial.",
      "options": ["Il y a", "Là-bas"],
      "correctAnswer": "Il y a",
      "language": "french",
      "level": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "____ c'est ?",
      "options": ["Qui est", "À qui est"],
      "correctAnswer": "Qui est",
      "language": "french",
      "level": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Je suis allé ___ ma sœur.",
      "options": ["leur", "là-bas"],
      "correctAnswer": "là-bas",
      "language": "french",
      "level": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Elle ___ comme médecin.",
      "options": ["travaille", "est"],
      "correctAnswer": "est",
      "language": "french",
      "level": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Ich habe mit ___ gesprochen.",
        "options": ["sie", "ihr"],
        "correctAnswer": "sie",
        "language": "german",
        "level": 0
      },
      {
        "question": "Woher ____ du?",
        "options": ["tust", "kommst"],
        "correctAnswer": "kommst",
        "language": "german",
        "level": 0
      },
      {
        "question": "Um wie viel Uhr steht sie ___ auf?",
        "options": ["auf", "aufs"],
        "correctAnswer": "auf",
        "language": "german",
        "level": 0
      },
      {
        "question": "Wo ___ er wohnen?",
        "options": ["tut", "wo"],
        "correctAnswer": "wo",
        "language": "german",
        "level": 0
      },
      {
        "question": "'Ich mag diesen Film ___.'",
        "options": ["sehe", "mag"],
        "correctAnswer": "mag",
        "language": "german",
        "level": 0
      },
      {
        "question": "Ich treffe sie ___ drei Uhr.",
        "options": ["am", "um"],
        "correctAnswer": "um",
        "language": "german",
        "level": 0
      },
      {
        "question": "Ostern ist im ___ März dieses Jahr.",
        "options": ["im", "in"],
        "correctAnswer": "im",
        "language": "german",
        "level": 0
      },
      {
        "question": "Sie ist ___ Arbeit den ganzen Tag heute.",
        "options": ["auf", "an"],
        "correctAnswer": "an",
        "language": "german",
        "level": 0
      },
      {
        "question": "Ich gehe ___ Bank, um Bargeld zu holen.",
        "options": ["an die", "zur"],
        "correctAnswer": "zur",
        "language": "german",
        "level": 0
      },
      {
        "question": "'Magst du das?'",
        "options":["'Ja, ich mag.'", "'Ja, das tue ich.'"],
        "correctAnswer": "'Ja, das tue ich.'",
        "language": "german",
        "level": 0
      },
      {
        "question": "Es ist die zweite Straße ___ der linken Seite.",
        "options": ["in", "auf"],
        "correctAnswer": "auf",
        "language": "german",
        "level": 0
      },
      {
        "question": "Er kommt ___ Bahnhof um sechs Uhr.",
        "options": ["am", "zum"],
        "correctAnswer": "am",
        "language": "german",
        "level": 0
      },
      {
        "question": "Ich ___, was sie sagt.",
        "options": ["kann nicht verstehen", "verstehe"],
        "correctAnswer": "kann nicht verstehen",
        "language": "german",
        "level": 0
      },
      {
        "question": "Sie lebt ___ Berlin.",
        "options": ["auf", "in"],
        "correctAnswer": "in",
        "language": "german",
        "level": 0
      },
      {
        "question": "Ich gehe ___ Bank, um Bargeld zu holen.",
        "options": ["an die", "zur"],
        "correctAnswer": "zur",
        "language": "german",
        "level": 0
      },
      {
        "question": "Ich bin ___ Fuß dorthin gegangen.",
        "options": ["in", "auf"],
        "correctAnswer": "zu",
        "language": "german",
        "level": 0
      },
      {
        "question": "____ ist ein Kino im Einkaufszentrum.",
        "options": ["Es", "Dort"],
        "correctAnswer": "Es",
        "language": "german",
        "level": 0
      },
      {
        "question": "____ ist das?",
        "options": ["Wer's", "Wessen"],
        "correctAnswer": "Wer's",
        "language": "german",
        "level": 0
      },
      {
        "question": "Ich ging ___ meiner Schwester.",
        "options": ["ihre", "dorthin"],
        "correctAnswer": "dorthin",
        "language": "german",
        "level": 0
      },
      {
        "question": "Sie ___ als Ärztin.",
        "options": ["travaille", "ist"],
        "correctAnswer": "ist",
        "language": "german",
        "level": 0
      },
      {
          "question": "मैंने ___ से बात की।",
          "options": ["उससे", "उसके साथ"],
          "correctAnswer": "उससे",
          "language": "hindi",
          "level": 0
        },
        {
          "question": "तुम कहां ___ हो?",
          "options": ["हो", "से"],
          "correctAnswer": "से",
          "language": "hindi",
          "level": 0
        },
        {
          "question": "वह कितने बजे उठती ___?",
          "options": ["है", "हैं"],
          "correctAnswer": "है",
          "language": "hindi",
          "level": 0
        },
        {
          "question": "वह कहां ___ रहता है?",
          "options": ["करता", "है"],
          "correctAnswer": "है",
          "language": "hindi",
          "level": 0
        },
        {
          "question": "'मुझे यह फिल्म ___ नहीं है।'",
          "options": ["देखनी", "पसंद"],
          "correctAnswer": "पसंद",
          "language": "hindi",
          "level": 0
        },
        {
          "question": "मैं उसे ___ बजे देख रहा हूँ।",
          "options": ["सुबह", "रात"],
          "correctAnswer": "सुबह",
          "language": "hindi",
          "level": 0
        },
        {
          "question": "इस साल पास्का ___ मार्च में है।",
          "options": ["पर", "में"],
          "correctAnswer": "में",
          "language": "hindi",
          "level": 0
        },
        {
          "question": "वह आज पूरे दिन ___ काम कर रही है।",
          "options": ["बिना रुके", "जागरूक"],
          "correctAnswer": "बिना रुके",
          "language": "hindi",
          "level": 0
        },
        {
          "question": "मैं बस से ___ जा रहा हूँ।",
          "options": ["स्कूल", "घर"],
          "correctAnswer": "घर",
          "language": "hindi",
          "level": 0
        },
        {
          "question": "'क्या तुम्हें यह पसंद है?'",
          "options":["'हां, मुझे पसंद है.'", "'हां, मैं यह पसंद करता हूँ.'"],
          "correctAnswer": "'हां, मुझे पसंद है.'",
          "language": "hindi",
          "level": 0
        },
        {
          "question": "यह दूसरी ओर ___ बड़ी सड़क है।",
          "options": ["सबसे छोटी", "पर"],
          "correctAnswer": "पर",
          "language": "hindi",
          "level": 0
        },
        {
          "question": "वह छह बजे ___ स्थानक पर आ रहा है।",
          "options": ["के पास", "पर"],
          "correctAnswer": "के पास",
          "language": "hindi",
          "level": 0
        },
        {
          "question": "मैं ___ वह क्या कह रही है।",
          "options": ["समझ नहीं पा रहा", "नहीं समझ सकता"],
          "correctAnswer": "नहीं समझ सकता",
          "language": "hindi",
          "level": 0
        },
        {
          "question": "वह लंदन ___ रही है।",
          "options": ["पर", "में"],
          "correctAnswer": "में",
          "language": "hindi",
          "level": 0
        }
]
      
    
  

